caskers.com 2019-06-28

# Privacy - Caskers

Caskers its affiliates and its subsidiaries (collectively, “we” or “Caskers”) is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. This privacy policy communicates how, when, and why we gather information about our customers and what we do with it. Please read this privacy policy carefully. If you do not agree to this privacy policy, please do not register, subscribe, create an account or otherwise interact with Caskers at www.caskers.com (the “Site”) or if you have, please immediately [ contact us](mailto:contact@caskers.com) to remove your account. By visiting the Site, you accept the practices described in this privacy policy.

If you have any questions about our privacy policies please contact us at [ contact@caskers.com](mailto:contact@caskers.com).

#### Information Collected

Caskers collects personal information (“Personal Information”) about members to customize the content and/or the layout of the Site and to contact members regarding their accounts. If a member chooses to place an order through the Site, we collect additional information including, but not limited to, the member’s name, billing address, shipping address, date of birth, date of order and product purchased.

Caskers also collects non-personal information (“Non-Personal Information”) and general statistics about each user and each member that visits the Site. This information is recorded, collected and analyzed to understand the usage of the Site. Non-Personal Information may include, but is not limited to, each users internet service provider, internet protocol address, browser information and other usage data. In addition, we automatically gather certain information about the use of the Site, such as how frequently certain areas of the Site are visited, including through the use of cookies, web beacons and other technologies (together, with “Personal Information” and “Non-Personal Information, the “Information”).

#### Use and Disclosure of Information

We will not share or disclose Information to anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy. Caskers may use Information to process and fulfill orders and to notify members and users of order status or products available for purchase on the Site. Caskers may, on occasion, share Information with third parties. In addition, we may share Information if we are required to do so by law or if disclosing Information is vital to identify, contact or bring legal action in order to protect Caskers, its customers or third parties. Information may also be used to develop personalized shopping experiences and histories for each member in order to customize products, promotions, emails, updates or special offers.

Information may be shared with merchants, vendors, retailers and any third party from whom the purchase is made, and may be provided to other third parties to process and fulfill orders. We have no control over how third parties use Information and assume no responsibility or liability for their use of Information.

On occasion, we may employ other third parties to perform services, maintain and operate the Site, maintain and operate updates or newsletters sent by Caskers or maintain certain features of the Site. We may also employ third parties to analyze our sales data or to assist in marketing and personalizing product information. We may share Information with any of these third parties. We may also transfer Information as an asset in connection with a proposed or actual merger, sale, corporate reorganization, stock sale or any other change in corporate structure. In such a circumstance, any transferee would be bound by the terms of this privacy policy.

Comments you voluntarily post on public forums such as our blog will be displayed publicly along with the name you submit and the time at which you submitted the comment. Although we reserve the right to monitor and delete any activity at our discretion, all Information posted is unprotected and can be seen by anyone.

If you elect to use our referral services for informing a friend about our Site, we ask you for the friend’s name and email address. Caskers will automatically send the friend an email inviting them to visit the Site. Caskers stores this Information for the purpose of, among others, sending emails and tracking the success of our referral program. The friend may contact Caskers at to request the removal of this information from our database.

#### Third Parties

Our Site may contain links to third party websites, products and services. Information collected by these third party websites is governed by their privacy policies and practices, if any, and is not subject to this privacy policy. We are not responsible for how these third party websites use information. If you visit a third party website from our Site, you do so at your own risk and we do not assume any responsibility or liability in connection therewith. We encourage you to become familiar about the privacy practices of any party, including Caskers, to whom you provide any information.

#### Minors

We do not knowingly collect Information about or from minors under the age of 21, nor do we or any of our third parties direct any solicitations or advertisements to minors. If you are not 21 or older, you are not authorized to use the Site. Parents should be aware that there are parental control tools available online that you can use to prevent your children from submitting information online without parental permission or from accessing material that is harmful to minors. If we learn that we collected Information about a minor, we will act to remove that Information.

#### How We Protect Your Information

We take reasonable precautions to safeguard your Information. While no computer system is completely secure, we believe the measures we have implemented reduce the likelihood of security problems to a level appropriate to the type of data involved.

When creating an account on our Site, you are required to establish a password. We courage you to choose a password that is at least 8 characters, using a combination of letters, numbers and symbols. You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your password and Information.

While we use standard security procedures and practices to safeguard Information, no Site is guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, we do not guarantee or attest to the security of Information, including your Information. If you transmit Information to Caskers, you do so at your own risk.

While we make efforts to accommodate requests to restrict our use of Information, we reserve the right to delete Information if we are not able to reasonably accommodate a requested restriction.

#### Removing Information

While we attempt to accommodate reasonable requests to delete Information, please note that we cannot always delete all records. For instance, we are required to retain records related to previous sales for financial reporting and compliance purposes. We may retain and use Information to, among other purposes, comply with our legal obligations, preserve our rights, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.

#### Privacy Policy Changes

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy for the Site, we will post the revised Privacy Policy here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we may disclose it to anyone. To the fullest extent permitted by law, your continued use of the Site indicates your assent to the Privacy Policy as posted.

#### Contact

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please [contact us](mailto:contact@caskers.com).
